Guide to the Front Page newspaper records, 1975-2006 and undated RL.00421
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Front Page newspaper records
1975-2006 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Bugle Publishing
RL.00421
116.9 Linear Feet
The Front Page (1979-2006) was a newspaper dedicated to the LGBTQ+ community in North and South Carolina. Collection consists of a large clippings file, research and subject files, newsletters, book publicity, correspondence, including letters to the editor, administrative records, a Kill box file, mailing lists, advertising layouts, photographs, a reader survey, faxes, some writings submissions, flyers, press releases, and files of other gay and lesbian publications. Other items include T-shirts, posters, and photographs. Topics represented include early research on AIDS, gay rights, resources for the community, legal and political issues, and pride events across the two states; there are also papers related to local activists and Front Page staff Lee Mullis and Jim Duley. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Historical Note
Founded by Jim Baxter in 1979 and based in Raleigh, North Carolina, The Front Page was a bi-monthly newspaper published by Bugle Publishing, Inc. devoted to the LGBTQ+ community in North and South Carolina. Its last issue was published in May 2006, after which it was absorbed by Charlotte-based newspaper QnotesCarolinas.
Jim Baxter (1953- ) went on to study journalism at Syracuse University after selling The Front Page to QnotesCarolinas. In September 2006, he became the first openly gay man to receive a distunguished alumnus award from his alma mater Guilford College. He also received the Front Page Award from QnotesCarolinas. Both awards recognized Baxter's significant contributions to the LGBTQ+ community in North Carolina and beyond.
Source: "Alma mater, publication honor student," The Daily Orange, October 2006, https://dailyorange.com/2006/10/alma-mater-publication-honor-student/ (accessed December 13, 2023).
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Front Page records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift from 1999-2008; as a gift from Jim Baxter in 2009 and 2018; and as a gift from Jim Duley Doerfler in 2023.
Collection Overview
Collection consists of materials used in production of the newspaper, specifically a large clippings file, flyers, newsletters, press releases, book PR, incoming correspondence, a Kill box file, some clippings organized by subject, papers centered on Lee Mullis and Jim Duley, a reader survey, faxes, some submissions, and a large number of other gay and lesbian publications.
Addition (2000-0304) (1 item, dated 1977) is a t-shirt designed by Tom Carr for the 1977 Southeastern Gay Conference in Chapel Hill, N.C.
Addition (2003-0036) (26,300 items; 43.5 lin. ft; dated 1975-2001 and undated) consists of periodicals, directories, clippings, press releases, advertising proofs, brochures, and other materials related to production of The Front Page and/or to gay/lesbian organizations, issues, and events throughout the U.S. Also includes subject and correspondence files; numerous issues of North Carolina Anvil from the late 1970s-early 1980s; a collection of drag photographs; direct mail materials; and several The Front Page, gay/lesbian, and event-themed t-shirts.
Addition (2008-0065) (2,500 items; 6 lin. ft.; 1970s-2006) includes reader surveys (mostly dated 1992); correspondence between readers and The Front Page; printed materials; gay pride and AIDS awareness posters; and miscellaneous materials and items.
Addition (2008-0245) (1,800 items; 2.4 lin. ft.; dated 1970s-1990s) contains research files; letters to the editor, 1980-1987; internal records; mailing lists; and printed materials. Several research files relate to early research and publicity of AIDS and the gay community in the 1980s.
Addition (2008-0287) (1,350 items; 1.8 lin. ft.; dated 1980-2004) includes organizational files, publications, and clippings from gay/lesbian associations and events.
Addition (2009-0162) (4 items; 0.1 lin. ft.; 1977-2002) includes a Cruise magazine (1977); The Loop newspaper (Charleston, 2002) and materials from the Guilford Green Foundation (2002).
Addition (2018-0020) (15.0 lin. ft) consists of materials related to the production of The Front Page, internal newspaper documentation, as well as materials documenting LGBT issues throught the United States.
Addition (2018-0063) (0.5 lin. ft.) includes correspondence, photographs, and articles on gay rights in North Carolina.
Addition (2023-0086) (3.5 lin. ft.; dated 1980-2004) contains photographs sent to and taken for The Front Page. The bulk of the photographs date from the 1990s and document Pride events, as well as other events such as conferences, protests, and marches. These photographs show a wide range of people, including: lesbian/gay parents and regional PFLAG (Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays) groups; bisexual and transgender people; drag performers; military personnel and veterans; gay men who self-identify as bears, leatherheads, and cowboys; lesbian women who self-identify as dykes; and supportive religious, racial, ethnic, interracial, and intersectional groups and organizations. Some of the individuals and organizations are identified, while others are not. A small portion of the photographs document homophobic activities and hate crimes, such as graffiti, anti-LGBTQ protest signs at Pride, and arson. Some of these photos contain harmful language.
Related Materials
Researchers may also be interested in the following materials at Duke:
William Wolfe, Jr. photographs of North Carolina Pride parades, 1996-2001.
The Front Page (HQ75 .F93).
Digitized issues of The Front Page are available through DigitalNC.org.
AIDS (Disease) -- United States -- History; Gay and lesbian rights; Gay and lesbian studies -- Periodicals; Gay community -- United States; Gay rights -- North Carolina; Gay rights -- South Carolina; Gays -- North Carolina; Gays -- South Carolina; Homosexuality -- Southern States; Homosexuality -- United States -- Periodicals; Lesbians -- North Carolina; Lesbians -- South Carolina; Lesbian community -- United States; Transsexualism -- United States; Transsexuals -- United States; North Carolina -- Social conditions -- 20th century; South Carolina -- Social conditions -- 20th century; Drag queens; Drag performance; Photographic prints; Lesbian mothers; Bears (Gay culture); Transgender people -- United States; AIDS activists; Gay pride parades -- United States -- Photographs; Gay pride celebrations; LGBT activism; Homophobia -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Gay rights -- Religious aspects; Gay military personnel; Christian gay people; Black LGBTQ+ people; Leathermen; LGBTQ+ people in the military; LGBTQ+ Christians; LGBTQ+ parents; Raleigh (N.C.); Doerfler, Jim Duley, 1965-; Baxter, Jim, 1953-; North Carolina anvil (Newspaper: Durham, N.C.); Front page (Newspaper: Raleigh, N.C.); Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
- Accession (1999-0421)
  - Clippings
    - 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - Primarily 1992 by month (Box 2)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 3)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 4)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 5)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 6)
    - 1984-1991 (Box 7)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 8)
    - 1980-1981, 1996 (Box 9)
    - 1982-1987, 1992 (Box 10)
    - 1992, Articles on AIDS up thru 1986 (Box 11)
    - 1983-1985; AIDS 1986-1988; 1995 (Box 12)
    - 1985, 1988-1990 (Box 13)
    - 1985, 1987, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - 1983-1987, 1998 (Box 15)
    - 1984-1989 (Box 16)
    - 1981-1990, 1996 (Box 17)
    - 1989- 1990 (Box 18)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 19)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 20)
    - 1985, 1998 (Box 21)
    - 1984-1988, 1998 (Box 22)
    - 1981, 1985-1990 (Box 23)
    - 1980-1981, 1994-1995 (Box 24)
    - 1991-1996 (Box 25)
    - 1991-1994 (Box 26)
    - 1983-1985, 1991-1994 (Box 27)
    - 1981-1984, 1989-1990 (Box 28)
    - 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 29)
    - 1981-1987 (Box 30)
    - 1980-1987 (Box 31)
    - 1982-1984, 1990-1991 (Box 32)
    - 1986-1987, 1991-1992 (Box 33)
    - 1980-1988 (Box 34)
    - 1984-1991 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous, late 1980s, 23 folders (Box 36)
    Scope and Contents note
    Primarily flyers, newsletters, press releases, and some submissions
  - Miscellaneous, 1987-1996, 21 folders (Box 37)
    Primarily flyers, newsletters, press releases, and book PR
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1996, 20 folders (Box 38)
    Primarily flyers, newsletters, and press releases
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1997, 20 folders (Box 39)
    Primarily newsletters, PR, and some incoming correspondence
  - Miscellaneous, 1996, 10 folders (Box 40)
  - Book publicity and Kill Box 1989-1996, 9 folders (Box 40)
  - Book publicity and Kill Box 1997, 13 folders (Box 41)
  - Clippings by subject, 1986, 26 folders (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1980s, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Clippings, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - AIDS articles (Box 42)
    - Jerry Falwell (Box 42)
  - Lee Mullis Papers, 12 folders (Box 42)
    Includes SE Conference ( ca. 1975) and Carolina Gay Association
  - Book catalogs, 1984-1994, 5 folders (Box 43)
  - Booklists (Box 43)
  - Book on tape (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous office files, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous files, 14 folders (Box 43)
    Primarily press releases, newsletters, handouts, and correspondence
  - Miscellaneous files, 20 folders (Box 44)
    Primarily press releases, newsletters, handouts, correspondence, and faxes
  - Miscellaneous files, 20 folders (Box 45)
    Primarily press releases, newsletters, and faxes
  - Miscellaneous files, 21 folders (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous files, 22 folders (Box 47)
    Primarily press releases, newsletters, correspondence, and faxes
  - Book publicity, 11 folders (Box 47)
  - Book publicity, 10 folders (Box 48)
  - Jim Duley Archives, 21 folders (Box 48)
    Any piece with Duley or Duley Papers belongs to this series
  - Jim Duley Archive, 41 folders (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous files (Box 50)
    Primarily book publicity, newsletters and some correspondence
  - Serials, 13 folders
    - Gala Review (Box 50)
    - Alternate (Box 50)
    - Genre (Box 50)
    - Affirmative (Box 50)
    - Manifest (Box 50)
    - David (Box 50)
  - Serials, 20 folders (Box 51)
    - David (Box 51)
    - Carolina Zipper (Box 51)
    - Altamont (Box 51)
    - The Charleston Alternative (Box 51)
    - Farce (Box 51)
    - Our South (Box 51)
    - The Newsletter (Box 51)
    - Q Notes (Box 51)
    - Time (Box 51)
    - In Unison (Box 51)
    - Low County Gallery (Box 51)
    - Fag Rag (Box 51)
    - Gay Sunshine (Box 51)
    - The Gay Alternative (Box 51)
    - Androgyny Review (Box 51)
    - Androgyny Newsletter (Box 51)
    - Action Magazine (Box 51)
    - Red Pages (Box 51)
    - Magnus (Box 51)
    - GPU News (Box 51)
    - Omega One (Box 51)
    - Feminary (Box 51)
    - Christopher Street (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous newsletters (Box 51)
  - Serials, 20 folders (Box 52)
    - Christopher Street (Box 52)
  - Serials, 20 folders (Box 53)
    - Dinah (Box 53)
    - Newsweek (Box 53)
    - I Know You Know (Box 53)
    - Inquiry (Box 53)
    - Time (Box 53)
    - EastWest (Box 53)
    - Black/Out (Box 53)
    - People (Box 53)
    - Yoga Journal (Box 53)
    - Image (Box 53)
    - Sisters (Box 53)
    - Sisters United (Box 53)
    - Forté (Box 53)
    - Empathy (Box 53)
    - The GLC News (Box 53)
    - The Illuminator (Box 53)
    - The Newsletter (Box 53)
    - The Charlotte Observer (Box 53)
    - Alabama Forum (Box 53)
    - Impact (Box 53)
    - Ebony (Box 53)
    - Malebox (Box 53)
    - Gays Preferred (Box 53)
    - Gay Scene (Box 53)
    - Gay Times (Box 53)
    - Mr. (Box 53)
    - Fag Rag (Box 53)
    - Arizona Gay News (Box 53)
    - Voice (Box 53)
    - California Voice (Box 53)
    - Gay Sunshine (Box 53)
    - San Diego's Pride (Box 53)
    - Gay Light (Box 53)
  - Serials (oversize) (Box 54)
    - Manifest (Box 54)
    - Alternate (Box 54)
    - Triangle Observer (Box 54)
    - Lambda (Box 54)
    - Parade (Box 54)
  - Serials (oversize) (Box 55)
    - Sunday Times Magazine (Box 55)
    - Lambda (Box 55)
    - Q Notes (Box 55)
    - In Unison (Box 55)
  - Serials (oversize) (Box 56)
    - In Unison (Box 56)
    - Q Notes (Box 56)
  - Serials (oversize) (Box 57)
    - Q Notes (Box 57)
    - Community Connections (Box 57)
    - Triangle Times (Box 57)
    - Q Notes (Box 57)
    - New York Native (Box 57)
    - News Midwest (Box 57)
  - Serials (oversize) (Box 58)
    - Gay (Box 58)
    - The Empty Closet (Box 58)
    - San Franciso Crusader (Box 58)
    - Gay Power (Box 58)
    - Out! (Box 58)
  - The Front Page Survey (Box 58)
    Completed to ascertain habits and political thinking of readers. Results were never used.
- Accession (2000-0304), 1977
  - Southeastern Gay Conference t-shirt, 1977 (Box Acc. 00/0304: Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    T-shirt designed by Tom Carr.
- Accession (2003-0036)
  - Contents of Boxes 1-7: (Box 1-7)
    - Directories (Box 1-7)
  - Contents of Box 8-11: (Box 8-11)
    - Subject Files, 1990s (Box 8-11)
  - Contents of Box 12-14: (Box 12-14)
    - Loose Material: Book Jackets and New Book Releases (Box 12-14)
  - Contents of Boxes 15-29: (Box 15-29)
    - Subject Files, 1990s (Box 15-29)
    - Loose Miscellaneous Material (Box 15-29)
  - Contents of Boxes 30-32: (Box 30-32)
    - Loose Miscellaneous Material, 1999-2000 (Box 30-32)
  - Contents of Boxes 33-44: (Box 33-44)
    - Clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 33-44)
  - Contents of Boxes 45-51: (Box 45-51)
    - Miscellaneous records, 1975-2001 (Box 45-51)
      Includes periodicals, press releases for film, television, music, and publishing, and brochures.
  - Contents of Boxes 52-55: (Box 52-55)
    - Issues of North Carolina Anvil, 1978-1983 (Box 52-55)
  - Contents of Boxes 56-58: (Box 56-58)
    - Newspapers, 1980s (Box 56-58)
      Includes issues of The Raleigh News & Observer, The Charlotte Observer, The Washington Post, and others.
  - Contents of Box 59: (Box 59)
    - Newspapers and news clippings, 1980s-2001 (Box 59)
  - Contents of Boxes 60-62: (Box 60-62)
    - Gay/Lesbian and The Front Page themed T-shirts (Box 60-62)
  - Contents of Boxes 62-97: (Box 62-97)
    - Miscellaneous records, 1987-2001 (Box 62-97)
      Includes press releases for film, television, music, and publishing; flyers and other publications related to Gay/Lesbian events; advertising proofs; rolodex cards; copies of Gay/Lesbian business directories (including The Front Page directory) and maps for various cities, and other publications and periodicals.
  - Contents of Boxes 98-99: (Box 98-99)
    - Direct Mail packets and Gay/Lesbian business directories (Box 98-99)
  - Drag Photographs (Box 100-102)
  - Protest Poster (Oversize-folder 1)
- Accession (2008-0065), 1970s-2006
  Addition (2008-0065) (2,500 items; 6 lin. ft.; 1970s-2006) includes reader surveys (mostly dated 1992); correspondence between readers and The Front Page; printed materials; gay pride and AIDS awareness posters; and miscellaneous materials and items.
  - Reader surveys, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Reader surveys, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Printed materials: booklets, folders, press releases (Box 2)
  - Printed materials (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 3)
  - Reader correspondence: mailings, feedback, classifieds (Box 4)
  - Administrative materials (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 5)
  - Printed materials (Box 5)
  - Posters (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Gay Men's Health Summit (Box 6)
    - Triangle Lesbian and Gay Pride March, 1986 (Box 6)
    - International March on the United Nations (Stonewall anniversary), New York City, 26 June 1994 (Box 6)
    - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 11 Oct 1987 (Box 6)
    - Charlotte Out, 1995 (Box 6)
    - March! New York City, 26 June 1994 (Box 6)
    - Silence = Death. Vote, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Crape Myrtle Festival, 2002 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride March, Asheville, 13 June 1992 (Box 6)
    - National Day of Mourning, 30 June 1989 (Box 6)
    - Stonewall to Raleigh: North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride March, Raleigh, 24 June 1989 (Box 6)
    - Pride '93 Schedule of Events, Raleigh (2 copies) (Box 6)
    - Out with Dignity, South Carolina Gay and Lesbian March, 20 June 1999 (2 copies) (Box 6)
    - Invisibility to equality: North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride, Charlotte, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Keep It Up (Friends For Life safe sex program) (Box 6)
    - Safety Pin (Friends For Life) (Box 6)
    - It's Time for a Man-to-Man Talk (Friends for Life) (Box 6)
    - Caricature (Box 6)
    - We've Got to Deal with This (Friends for Life) (Box 6)
    - Speaking for Ourselves: North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride March, Durham, 29 June 1991 (Box 6)
    - 10 Million People were Murdered in Nazi Death Camps - prisoner badge chart, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Word to the Wise: Condoms can save lives (Friends for Life) (Box 6)
    - Pink Triangle (Nazis), 1995 (Box 6)
    - South Carolina Gay and Lesbian Pride March, Columbia, 19 June 1993 (Box 6)
    - Bigotry Kills: Stop Jesse Helms, 1990 (Box 6)
    - South Carolina Gay and Lesbian Pride Festival, Columbia, April 1996 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride '88, Raleigh, 25 June 1988 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride March, Chapel Hill/Carrboro, 30 June 1990 (Box 6)
    - You're Among Friends (Friends for Life), 2006 (Box 6)
    - Demand Safer AIDS Drugs (Box 6)
- Accession (2008-0245), 4 boxes
  Addition (2008-0245) (1,800 items; 2.4 lin. ft.; dated 1970s-1990s) contains research files; letters to the editor, 1980-1987; internal records; mailing lists; and printed materials. Original folder titles have, for the most part, been retained.
  - Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
  - TFP - General Procedures (Box 1)
  - TFP - Internal (Box 1)
  - TFP - Financial (Box 1)
  - Mailing lists (Box 1)
  - Hunt, Helms, etc. (Box 2)
  - Hunt, Helms, 1984 Election (Box 2)
  - Clippings (Box 2)
  - Relationship Contract (Box 2)
  - POA (Power of Attorney) (Box 2)
  - Wills (Box 2)
  - Brochures (Box 2)
  - Baxter notes (Box 2)
  - Clippings, letters (Box 2)
  - C.A.N. (Box 2)
  - AIDS (Box 2)
  - AIDS education (Box 2)
  - Safe sex ads (Box 2)
  - Surveys (Box 2)
  - Misc. N.C. groups (Box 2)
    Includes copies of newsletters written by incarcerated people (not specifically LGBT) published in Asheville, NC.
  - Violence and vandalism (Box 3)
  - Anti-gay violence - Male (Box 3)
  - Safety - Anti-gay violence (Box 3)
  - Speaker's bureau (Box 3)
  - Child abuse (Box 3)
  - Dispute settlement (Box 3)
  - Various organizations (Box 3)
  - Sexism - various materials (Box 3)
  - John and Jim's correspondence with prospective writers, 1980-1982 (Box 3)
  - Syndicated materials (Box 3)
  - Printed materials, 1980s (Box 4)
  - Letters to the editor, 1980-1987 (Box 4)
  - Photographs (Box 4)
- Accessions (2008-0287) and (2009-0162), 1977-2004; 3 boxes
  Addition (2008-0287) (1,350 items; 1.8 lin. ft.; 1980-2004) includes organizational files, publications, and clippings from gay/lesbian associations and events.
  Addition (2009-0162) (4 items; 0.1 lin. ft.; 1977-2002) includes a Cruise magazine (1977); The Loop newspaper (Charleston, 2002) and materials from the Guilford Green Foundation (2002).
  - Loose materials: publications, reprints, and clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 1)
  - Loose materials (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Triangle Business and Professional Guild (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Triangle Area Gay Scientests (TAGS) (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Triad Health Project (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Teachout LEO (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Stonewall Dinner (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Southern Appalachian Lesbian and Gay Alliance (SALGA) (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - RFO (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - QCF News (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Prison conditions (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Pride 1988 (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Pride 1990 (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Palmetto Gay and Lesbian Association (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence (NCARRV) (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Health Project (LGHP) (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Metropolitan Community Church (MCC) (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Metrolina Community Service Project (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Menamore (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Guilford Alliance for Gay and Lesbian Equality (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Gourmet Club (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - GROW (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Capital Area Business and Professional Association (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Black Lesbians and Gays (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Lightning Brown (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Loose materials (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 2)
  - Community Centers (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Crazy Owl (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - NCHRF (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Crape Myrtle (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Human Rights Campaign dinner, 2004 (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - SC Gay/Lesbian Pride (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - House insurance (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - David H. Perry (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Community Centers (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - In Unison (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Bob Page (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Celebrating our history (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - David Magazine, 1999 Jan., 3 issues (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Carolina's Hotspots Magazine, no. 7 (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - LGHP (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Epson-nelms, Craig (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Brian Cochran (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Bill James (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
  - Guilford Green Foundation and miscellaneous publications, 1977-2002 (Box Acc. 08/287: Box 3)
- Accession (2018-0020)
  Addition (2018-0020) (15.0 lin. ft) consists of materials related to the production of The Front Page, internal newspaper documentation, as well as materials documenting LGBT issues throught the United States.
  - Box 1 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 1)
  - Box 2 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 2)
  - Box 3 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 3)
  - Box 4 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 4)
  - Box 5 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 5)
  - Box 6 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 6)
  - Box 7 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 7)
  - Box 8 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 8)
  - Box 9 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 9)
  - Box 10 (Box Acc. 2018/0020: Box 10)
- Accession (2018-0063)
  Addition (2018-0063) (0.5 lin. ft.) includes correspondence, photographs, and articles on gay rights in North Carolina.
  - Correspondence (Box Acc. 2018/0063: Box 1)
  - Photographs (Box Acc. 2018/0063: Box 1)
  - Congregations in Conflict book (Box Acc. 2018/0063: Box 1)
  - Articles on gay rights in North Carolina (Box Acc. 2018/0063: Box 1)
- Photographs (Accession 2023-0086), 1980-2004
  Accession consists of photographs sent to and taken for The Front Page. The bulk of the photographs date from the 1990s and document Pride events, as well as other events such as conferences, protests, and marches. These photographs show a wide range of people, including: lesbian/gay parents and regional PFLAG (Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays) groups; bisexual and transgender people; drag performers; military personnel and veterans; gay men who self-identify as bears, leatherheads, and cowboys; lesbian women who self-identify as dykes; and supportive religious, racial, ethnic, interracial, and intersectional groups and organizations. Some of the individuals and organizations are identified, while others are not. A small portion of the photographs document homophobic activities and hate crimes, such as graffiti, anti-LGBTQ protest signs at Pride, and arson. Some of these photos contain harmful language.
  Arrangement